Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
- Box: 44, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 55: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: May 6, 1985.
  - Item 56: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 57: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: May 15, 1985.
  - Item 58: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 59: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: July 12, 1985.
  - Item 60: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: July 24, 1985.
  - Item 61: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 62: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Aug. 30, 1985.
  - Item 63: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 64: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 65: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Sept. 25, 1985.
  - Item 66: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 67: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Oct. 24, 1985.
  - Item 68: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 69: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Nov. 7, 1985.
  - Item 70: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 71: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Dec. 23, 1985.
  - Item 72: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 73: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Jan. 17, 1986.
  - Item 74: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 75: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Jan. 23, 1986.
  - Item 76: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Feb. 11, 1986.
  - Item 77: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 78: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 79: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 80: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 81: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 82: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 83: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 84: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 85: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 86: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 87: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 88: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: April 24, 1986.
  - Item 89: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 90: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: May 14, 1986.
  - Item 91: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: June 6, 1986.
  - Item 92: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 93: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: June 23, 1986.
  - Item 94: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 95: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: June 24, 1986.
  - Item 96: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 97: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: July 7, 1986.
  - Item 98: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 99: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: July 24, 1986.
  - Item 100: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 101: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Aug. 29, 1986.
  - Item 102: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 103: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Sept. 15, 1986.
  - Item 104: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 105: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 106: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 107: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 108: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 109: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 110: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 111: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 112: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 113: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 114: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 115: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 116: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 117: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 118: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 119: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 120: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 121: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 122: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 123: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 124: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 125: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 126: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 127: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 128: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 129: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 130: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 131: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 132: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 133: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 134: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 135: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 136: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 137: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 138: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 139: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 140: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 141: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 142: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 143: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 144: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 145: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 146: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 147: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 148: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 149: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 150: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 151: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 152: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 153: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 154: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 155: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 156: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 157: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 158: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 159: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 160: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 161: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 162: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 163: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 164: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 165: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 166: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 167: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 168: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 169: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 170: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 171: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 172: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 173: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 174: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 175: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 176: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 177: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 178: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 179: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 180: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 181: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 182: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 183: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 184: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 185: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1985; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 186: President's Address: United, Towards a Working Recovery, Fifteenth Consitutional Convention, 1984; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 187: President's Address: United, Towards a Working Recovery, Fifteenth Consitutional Convention, 1984; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 188: Agenda, B.C. Federation of Labour, Conference - B.C. 1986 Equity or Status Quo?, "An Inquiry into the Impact of Provincial Politics on Women's Issues", Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 189: Agenda, B.C. Federation of Labour, Conference - B.C. 1986 Equity or Status Quo?, "An Inquiry into the Impact of Provincial Politics on Women's Issues", Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 190: B.C. Federation of Labour, Conference - B.C. 1986 - Equity or Status Quo?, Rules of Order, Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 191: B.C. Federation of Labour, Conference - B.C. 1986 - Equity or Status Quo?, Rules of Order, Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 192: Draft, August 6, 1985, Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Author: Terry Segarty
    Notes: (correspondence: Segarty to Kube)
  - Item 193: Draft, August 6, 1985, Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 194: Hot from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: October 30, 1980, To All Affiliates
  - Item 195: Hot from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1980; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 196: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 197: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 198: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 199: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Dec. 22, 1986.
  - Item 200: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1986; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 201: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Apr. 7, 1987.
  - Item 202: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 203: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Apr. 8, 1987.
  - Item 204: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 205: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Apr. 10, 1987.
  - Item 206: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 207: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 208: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 209: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Apr. 16, 1987.
  - Item 210: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 211: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: June 9, 1987.
  - Item 212: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 213: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 214: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 215: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: July 7, 1987.
  - Item 216: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 217: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: July 16, 1987.
  - Item 218: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: July 31, 1987.
  - Item 219: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 220: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Sept. 2, 1987.
  - Item 221: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 222: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Sept.10, 1987.
  - Item 223: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 224: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Nov. 18, 1987.
  - Item 225: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1987; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 226: News from the B.C. Federation of Labour, 1988; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Notes: Annual convention Nov. 28-Dec. 2, 1988.
- Box: 44, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Master Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees: The Engineering, Technical, and Inspectional, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
    Author: British Columbia Government Employees' Union
  - Item 2: Master Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees: The Engineering, Technical, and Inspectional, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Master Agreement between the Government of the Province of Alberta and the Alberta Union of Provincial Employees: The Administrative, Fiscal, and Regulatory Component..., 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Master and Component Agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia.: The Environment, Resources, and Conservation Component, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Master and Component Agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia.: The Correctional Services Component of the B.C. Government Employees' Union, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Master and Component Agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia.: The Marine Services (Highways and Forests)., 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Box: 44, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Master and Component Agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia.: The retail Stores and Warehouse Component, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Master and Component Agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia.: The Marine Services (Highways and Forests)., 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Master and Component Agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia.: The Correctional Services Component, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Master and Component Agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia.: The Educational and Scientific Services Component, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Master and Component Agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia.: The Social and Health Services Component, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Master and Component Agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia.: The Environment, Resources, and Conservation Component, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Grievance Investigation Manual, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Grievance Investigation Manual, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Box: 44, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Master agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia represented by the Government Employee Relations Bureau and the Administrative Support Component of the B.C. Government Employees' Union, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Master agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia represented by the Government Employee Relations Bureau and the Trades and Crafts Component of the B.C. Government Employees' Union, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Master agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia represented by the Government Employee Relations Bureau and the Administrative, Fiscal, and Regulatory Component of the B.C. Government Employees' Union, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Master agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia represented by the Government Employee Relations Bureau and the Hospital and Allied Services Component of the B.C. Government Employees' Union, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Master agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia represented by the Government Employee Relations Bureau and the Educational and Scientific Services Component of the B.C. Government Employees' Union, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Master agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia represented by the Government Employee Relations Bureau and the Trades and Crafts Component of the B.C. Government Employees' Union, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Box: 44, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Master agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia represented by the Government Employee Relations Bureau and the Hospital and Allied Services Component of the B.C. Government Employees' Union, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Master agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia represented by the Government Employee Relations Bureau and the Retail Stores and Warehouse Component of the B.C. Government Employees' Union, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Master agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia represented by the Government Employee Relations Bureau and the Social and Health Services Component of the B.C. Government Employees' Union, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Master agreement between the Government of the Province of British Columbia represented by the Government Employee Relations Bureau and the Administrative Support Component of the B.C. Government Employees' Union, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Constitution and bylaws, 1977; Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Agreement between the Public Service Commission and the British Columbia Government Professional Employees' Association: Dated: June 20, 1975, Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Box: 44, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Canadian Air Traffic Control Association, 1973; Publication (Box 44, Folder 14)
    Author: Canadian Air Traffic Control Association
  - Item 2: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada, 1973; Publication (Box 44, Folder 14)
    Author: Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada
  - Item 3: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Canadian Air Traffic Control Association, 1970; Publication (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Box: 44, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The role of international unionism in Canada, 1967; Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
    Author: John H. G. Crispo